American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File 5001 PAM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 3, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: What Compulsary Health Insurance Would Mean to the Druggist, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Author: Harry B. Mason
  - Item 8: Women's Health Insurance, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Health Insurance: A New Bill, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: "The Proper Study of Mankind is Man", 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Medical Provisions of the Tentative Draft of an Act for Health Insurance, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Health Insurance Standards and Tentative Draft of an Act, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Membership Constitution By-Laws, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: The Need for Health Insurance, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Author: Irving Fisher
  - Item 15: Hearing on Mills Health Insurance Bill - before Senate Judiciary Committee, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Author: John F. Crowell
- Box: 3, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: First National Conference of Health Insurance Commissioners, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Resolution, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: "Mills Bill", 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Campaign of 1917, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Duluth, Minnesota 1917, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Health Insurance, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Resolution passed Oregon Legislative Le ague, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Compulsary "Welfare Insurance", 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: As Seen from the Side Lines, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: F.R. Sheri
  - Item 10: Report of Committee on Health Insurance, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Resolution, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Garment Workers Favor Compulsory, Health Insurance, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: George M. Price
  - Item 13: Extract fron Proceedings Thirty-Fifth Annual Convention, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Resolution, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Resolution, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: Jonathan Pearson
  - Item 16: Extract from the Proceedings of the Minnesota State Federation of Labor Convention, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Resolution, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: I. Sylvester
  - Item 18: Report of Committee on Health Insurance, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: John A. Phillips
  - Item 19: Report of Committee on Health Insurance, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: Synopsis of Report of the Committee on Social and other Forms of State Insurance to the National Fraternal Congress of America, Chicago, August, 1917, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 21: Resolution Passed, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: Resolution - Brooklyn Civic Club, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: Theodore F. Moench
  - Item 23: Resolved, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: Resolution 55, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 25: Resolutions adopted by the Portland Congregational Ministeral Brotherhood, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: Resolution 25, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: Henry Abrahams
  - Item 27: Resolution Received fro the Council of Jewish Women of Pittsburgh, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 28: At a meeting of the Medical Society of the County of Schenectady, held on January 16th, 1917, the following resolution was adopted, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 29: Report of the Committee on Health Insurance; Convention in Philadelphia, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 30: "Shop Dividends due to Personal Work", 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: Thomas T. Read
  - Item 31: Report of the Committee on Health Insurance of the American Association of Industrial Physicians and Surgeons, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 32: Report on Health Insurance Laws Committee of Society of Medical Jurisprudence, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 33: Fallacies of Compulsory Health Insurance, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 34: Compulsory Health Insurance, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: Magnus W. Alexander
  - Item 35: Progress Toward Health Insurance, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 36: Health Insurance Officially Endorsed, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 37: Health Insurance Officially Endorsed, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 38: What will Health Insurance do for The American Citizen?, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: Miles M. Dawson
  - Item 39: The Medical Profession and Social Progress, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 40: Reply to Dr. Samuel J. Kopetzky, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Box: 3, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Health Insrance Discussion Executive Council Meeting, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Health Insurance Advantages to Industry, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Health Insurance and the Hospitals, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Health Insurance, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Proceedings of the Eleventh Annual Session of the West Virginia, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Memorandum New York State Federation of Labor, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Resolution adopted by the Executive Council, American Federation of Labor, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Recommendation of Legislative Committee, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Author: Howell Wright
  - Item 9: Proposition No. 118, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Author: Delegate Campbell
  - Item 10: Proposition No. 118 File Copy, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Labor Legislative Program adopted by the State Conference on Reconstruction, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Recommendation of Legislative Committee Adapted by Convention of American Hospital Association, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Memorandum New York State Federation of Labor, Tentative Offline Calls Act for Workmen's Health Insurance, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Resolution Adopted by the American Hospital Association at Atlantic City, September 27th, 1918., Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 15: Resolution Adopted by the American Hospital Association at Atlantic, September 27th, 1918. File Copy, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 16: Health Insurance for Workingmen, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 17: Resolution on Health Insurance, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 18: Health Insurance, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 19: Resolution on Health Insurance, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 20: Resolution on Health Insurance Legislation, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 21: Resolution No. 4, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 22: Resolution, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 23: Resolution, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 24: Resolutions and Recommendations, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 25: Health Insurance, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 26: General Executive Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 27: Medical Research Committee, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 28: Health Insurance Statements of Prominent Persons, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Box: 3, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Minority Report + Medical Society Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Program of the Public Health Service, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Women's Joint Legislative Conference, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: At a special meeting of the Medical Society of the County of Erie held May 2nd, 1919, the following resolutions were unanimously adopted:, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Author: James E. King
  - Item 5: Heakth Promotion Through Legislation for Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: The American Political Science Review, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Report of the Health Insurance Commission to the General Assembly of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Minority Report of reconstruction Commission of New York State on Compulsory Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Author: J.N. Beckley
  - Item 9: The Health Insurance Bill, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Box: 3, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Social Insurance Dept., 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Health Insurance and the Public, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Author: Frederick L. hoffman
  - Item 3: Minority Report of Reconstruction Commission of New York State on Compulsory Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Kings county Dental Society Meeting, Brooklyn, 23 October 1919, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Resolution No. 606, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Author: William Green
  - Item 6: Universal Workmen's Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Resolution on Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Resolution No. 4 Universal Workmen's Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Author: O, M, Partelow
  - Item 9: Universally Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Resolution No. 606, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Workingmen's Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: Resolved, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: A Plan for a More Effective Federal and State Health Administration, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Box: 3, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Compilation of Insurance and Medical Aid Acts, 1926; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Notes on the Hearing of the Davenport Health Insurance Bill, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Author: Mark Daly
  - Item 3: For Immediate Release, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: National Health Insurance Act (U.K.), 1928; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: What Employe Health Service Costs, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Social Insurance, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Author: Dr. John B. Andrews
- Box: 3, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: H.J. Resolutions, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Resolutions Adopted by Executive Council (N.Y. Fed. Of Labor), 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Maine State Federation of Labor Universal Health Insurance, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Resolved, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: J.W. Schereschewsky
  - Item 5: Resolved, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Health Insurance, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: health Insurance, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Special Meeting of the New York State Fraternal Congress, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: A Health Program for Organizaed Labor, 1921; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: Grace M. Bernheim
  - Item 10: Report of Investigation into the Operation of the British Health Insurance Act, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: William T. Ramsey
  - Item 11: Health Insurance, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: Velue of Health Service In Industry Proven, 1921; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 13: Effects of Compulsory Health Insurance on the Practice of Medicine, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: M. L. Harris
  - Item 14: Further Objections to Compulsory Health Insurance, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: Edward H. Ochsner
  - Item 15: Report of Investigation into the Operation of the British Health Insurance Act, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Box: 3, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Sickness Insurance and Medical Care, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: Michael M. Davis
  - Item 2: Health Insurance, 1935; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: Rose Schneiderman
  - Item 3: Social Planning and the Medical Sciences, 1935; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: California's Medical Mix-Up, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: Philip King Brown
  - Item 5: Project Budget - 1932, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: The Purchase of Medical Care Throuigh Fixed Periodic Payments, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: Pierce Williams
  - Item 7: California - Senate Committee on Investigation of the High Cost of Sickness, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: News Digest, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: December Survey Graphic Magazine of Social Interpretation, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: The American Approach to Health Insurance, 1911; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: The Health of the Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: Lee. K Frankel
  - Item 12: Some Aspects of National Health Insurance, 1923; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: Alexander Gray
  - Item 13: Cost of Medical Care, 1928; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: Lee K. Frankel
- Box: 3, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Vital Speeches of the Day, 1938; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Author: Dr. Nathan B. Van Etten
  - Item 2: The Need for a National Health Program, 1938; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Summary of the Health Insurance Act, 1936; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Toward Better National Health, 1938; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Granite Cutters' Journal, 1938; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Uncle Sam, M.D., 1937; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Author: Paul A. Williams
  - Item 7: Health Insurance, 1939; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Author: Joseph Hirsh
  - Item 8: The National Health Program: Next Great Social Goal, 1939; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Agreement - Medical Guild Foundation, Inc. and Physician, 1940; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: The Eastern Underwriter, 1940; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Labor Clarion, 1941; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Compulsory Health Insurance and Disease Control, 1937; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Author: Frederick L. Hoffman, LL.D.
- Box: 4, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: One Day of Rest in Seven, 1907; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Rational hours of Work, 1913; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: A.H. Crosfield
  - Item 3: One Day of Rest in Seven, 1907; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The Day of Rest Law, 1914; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: James M. Lynch
  - Item 5: Speech of Hon. Andrew J. Peters, 1913; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: "Some Practical Experiences in Shortening Hours of Labor", 1915; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Frederick R. Hazard
  - Item 7: Stenographic Record Public Hearing, 1916; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Information Guide of the Culinary Industry, 1916; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Medical Organization Under Health Insurance, 1916; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Alexander Lambert, M.D.
  - Item 10: The Saturday Half-Holiday, 1915; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Box: 4, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Sickness Insurance or Sickness Prevention?, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Labor and the Sabbath, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Author: Solon De Leon
  - Item 3: In Re. Length of Lunch Period for Female Employes, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Hours - Page 7, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Government Contracts and the Federal Eight Hour Law, 1917; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Night Work For Women, 1921-1922 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: "The Three-Shift Day in the Steel Industry", 1920; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Author: Horace B. Drury
  - Item 8: Night Work Laws for Women, 1920; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Says Five-Hour Day Brings Best Results, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Author: Prof. Hobhouse
  - Item 10: Legal Working Hours for Women - Weekly, 1920; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Program The Long Day in the Steel Industry A Problem in the Engineering of Men, 1920; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Memorandum - 8 Hour Day for Women, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Ten-Hours Laws for Women Workers, 1919; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Chart 1, 1919; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Chart 2, 1919; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Chart 7, 1919; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Digest of the Eight-Hour Bill, 1919; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Sickness Insurance or Sickness Prevention?, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: 8-Hour Workday republicans Fought Now in Effect, 1919; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Hours of Labor for Women and Children, 1917; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: The Maximum Annual Hours Bills or The Overtime Vacation Labor Bill, 1919; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Author: H. Crouse Bennetch
- Box: 4, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Calendar of the Twelve-Hour Day in the Steel Industry, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Hours of Labor of Women, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Author: Maud Swett
  - Item 3: Scrapper O'Doon, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Author: R.G. Kirk
  - Item 4: Night Work Laws For Women, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Legal Working Hours for Women -- Daily, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Legal Hours of Work of Women in Hotels, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Experience with the Five Day Week Based Upon A Questionnaire, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Prevention of War and Poverty, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Senate Bill 303, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Abolish Seven-Day Labor, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Resolution One Day of Rest in Seven, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Do Women Need Shorter Hours Than Men Do?, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: People of New York on the Relation of Charles Deutermann, against, William J. Doylw, as Sheriff of the County of Westchester, 1913; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Box: 4, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of the Committee on a Uniform Act For One Day of Rest in Seven, 1924; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Eight-hour Day in the United States, 1924; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Hours of Service Regulations, 1938; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Memorandum on the Forty-Wight Hour Week For Women, 1926; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: James A. Hamilton
  - Item 5: Pendind Legislation to Regulate Women's Hours of Labor, 1927; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: "Labor's Proposals Submitted to Labor Laws Commission" and "Our State Eight-Hour and Prevailing Wage Law Upheld, 1926; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Minutes of the Organization Meeting of the Committee for Shorter Working Hours in Manufacturing Industries in the South, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: In the Matter of Maximum Hours of Service of Motor Carrier Employees, 1938; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: W.P. Bartel
  - Item 9: (Suggested) Rules and Regulations Governing Compressed Air Work-(Submitted for Committee on Compressed Air, 1930; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: What Shorter Work Hours Means To The Railroad Industry, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: A.F. Whitney
  - Item 11: What Greater Work Hours Mean to The Railroad Industry, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Explanation of 44 hour week bill, 1933; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Statement bu Mark A. Daly for Associated Industries, 1925; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: Mark A. Daly
  - Item 14: Shackled The Minimum Wage and The Eight Hour Day, 1924; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Summary of a Brief Prepared by the Joint Legislative Conference in Support of 48-Hour Law for Women, 1926; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Memorandum on the Forty-Eight Hour Week for Women, 1926; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: How Broken Pledges Defeated the 48-Hour Week in New York State, 1925; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Shall There Be Special Restrictive Laws for Women?, 1927; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Memorandum Filed with Assembly Bill, Introductory Number 1142, 1925; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: Alfred S. Smith
  - Item 20: An Act (To Amend the Labor Law), 1933; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: The Eight Hour Bill, 1906; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Box: 4, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Statement of Mrs. Mary Grace Quackenbos, Attorney and Counselor at Law, New York, N.Y., 1910; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Memorandum Submitted by the Labor Information Office for Italians, 1909; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: Oscar S. Straus
  - Item 3: Steerage Legislation, 1910; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Abstract of the Report on Contract Labor and Induced and Assisted Immigration, 1911; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Abstract of the Report on Importation and Harboring of Women for Immoral Purposes, 1910; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Abstract of the Report on The Immigration Situation in Other Countries, 1910; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: North American Civic League for Immigrants, 1913; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: A Minimum Wage Law for Immigrants, 1911; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: Paul U. Kellogg
  - Item 9: The United States Immigration Commission, 1908; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Abstract of the Report on Immigration Conditions in Hawaii, 1910; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Brief Statement of the Conclusions and Recommendations of the Immigrant Commission with Views of the Minority, 1910; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Abstract of the Report on Changes in Bodily Form of Descendants of Immigrants, 1911; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Peonage and the Treatment and Conditions of Work of Immigrants, 1911; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Notaries Public and Immigrants, 1909; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: New York-New Jersey Committee, 1911; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Box: 4, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Immigration Speech of Hon. Frank Buchanan, 1912; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Author: Frank Buchanan
  - Item 2: Speech of Hon. William Kent of California, 1912; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)